[
  {
    "date": "2026-01-21",
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "11 \u00d7 16",
        "answer": 176
      },
      {
        "question": "31% of 200",
        "answer": 62
      },
      {
        "question": "5 + 47",
        "answer": 52
      },
      {
        "question": "35% of 200",
        "answer": 70
      },
      {
        "question": "11 + 5",
        "answer": 16
      },
      {
        "question": "61% of 200",
        "answer": 122
      },
      {
        "question": "15 \u00d7 35",
        "answer": 525
      },
      {
        "question": "87% of 200",
        "answer": 174
      },
      {
        "question": "5 \u00d7 20",
        "answer": 100
      },
      {
        "question": "97% of 200",
        "answer": 194
      }
    ],
    "scores": [
      {
        "username": "suraj",
        "score": 331
      }
    ]
  }
]